<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Secret Room on The Nook &amp; Cranny Digest</title>
    <link>https://www.nookandcrannydigest.com/tags/secret-room/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Secret Room on The Nook &amp; Cranny Digest</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 11:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.nookandcrannydigest.com/tags/secret-room/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Agent X: The VP&#39;s HQ</title>
      <link>https://www.nookandcrannydigest.com/5-agent-x-the-vp-hq/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 11:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nookandcrannydigest.com/5-agent-x-the-vp-hq/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;ll have to excuse the melodramatic nature of this one, it&amp;rsquo;s a great hidden room with an exceptional entrance but it can be a little over-the-top at times.
The video below comes from the pilot episode of Agent X. In it, the newly appointed Vice President of the United States discovers the secret entrance to a hidden tunnel and subsequent hidden rooms within her new house.
Video   Images The seemingly inocuous wall containing the entrance to a secret tunnel and subsequent rooms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sherlock Holmes: The Powder Room</title>
      <link>https://www.nookandcrannydigest.com/4-sherlock-holmes-the-powder-room/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 20:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nookandcrannydigest.com/4-sherlock-holmes-the-powder-room/</guid>
      <description>Given the nature and reputation of Sherlock Holmes one would expect to find many more examples of hidden rooms and other intriguing nooks and crannies in this and the subsequent movie but, alas, this is just about all we get. There is a stereotypical safe behind a picture frame found in Sherlocks&amp;rsquo; office but it comes and goes so quickly that I didn&amp;rsquo;t see fit to include it here. If you&amp;rsquo;re curious, you can see it at about minute twenty-eight of the movie (28:45).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr. &amp; Mrs. Smith: His and Hers Weapons Caches</title>
      <link>https://www.nookandcrannydigest.com/3-mr-and-mrs-smith-his-and-hers-weapons-caches/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nookandcrannydigest.com/3-mr-and-mrs-smith-his-and-hers-weapons-caches/</guid>
      <description>Let this be a lesson to you. If you&amp;rsquo;re married you should probably invest in a secret weapons cache hidden in or near your home, just in case your significant other turns out to be a hitman/hitwoman.
Joking aside, Mr. and Mrs. Smith hosts a treasure trove of secret rooms and hidden compartments for him and her so whatever your style you&amp;rsquo;ll probably find one that suits you in this movie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>V for Vendetta: The Relic Room</title>
      <link>https://www.nookandcrannydigest.com/2-v-for-vendetta-the-relic-room/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 13:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nookandcrannydigest.com/2-v-for-vendetta-the-relic-room/</guid>
      <description>This one&amp;rsquo;s a great one but it goes by so quick that if you blink while you&amp;rsquo;re watching the movie you may miss it the first time around. This nook/cranny comes from the movie V for Vendetta (2005). In this scene Evey (Natalie Portman) has fled from the police and has gone to Gordon Deitrich&amp;rsquo;s (Stephen Fry; her friend/boss and a famous/wealthy TV personality) home for refuge. She realizes how this may bring unwanted attention to him and begins to apoligize for coming to him when he reveals his secret &amp;ldquo;relic room&amp;rdquo; and convinces her that she has nothing to worry about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI: The Hidden Room Behind The Wainscoting</title>
      <link>https://www.nookandcrannydigest.com/1-csi-the-hidden-room-behind-the-wainscoting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 20:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nookandcrannydigest.com/1-csi-the-hidden-room-behind-the-wainscoting/</guid>
      <description>This is the first post of The Nook &amp;amp; Cranny Digest. The beginning. The best place to start is at the beginning, or so they say. For this first post I decided it would only be right to go back to the beginning of my fascination with all things even tangentially related to secret passageways, hidden rooms, trap doors, secret compartments, and even little nooks and crannies not immediately apparent to the casual observer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>